I welcome back to the wheel of life
online retreat hi Slama data quality i
rep rep online Roddick ahead of pun and
I'm happy that Stanley stress a firm
again Thank You Stan Lee media dependent
Messiah Lanka the name of this session
is dead end dead end beginning
namaste near the La Jolla Punto de Molay
that n means locked away Telugu to
bratty jalander humbug so the picture
you see here is an alleyway as nearest
to the D company I don't have this scene
near the lass of Aughrim gel on some
people and somebody put a also wall
there and you can't go anything the Sun
at it up with sunblock on the beach oh
and this whole class is gonna be you
know how is it that you think tanks are
and dr. Lahiri combined and then about
half I see the class will girl switch
horses and go in a different way
Vanakkam audience laughs Nigel and
catechin Brigante cougar and magic
mentoring bro beta Simba kiss attaining
some joy to me so here's the third
section about you know how how is it
that we have such trouble in this life
he began Kathy Guttenberg Yemenites are
akito-kun a masala Della bitta peeny and
means of joy here is an interesting
idiom any other lots of or MDM young man
re and it means how he makes a crossing
into a new life like crossing a river
into a new country into broth it's our
Academy Nia Branca cleared open bar ooh
super teen Manya Brown is soon icon
Agora borough
killings in so there are different ways
to take birth like egg a table pots are
on Dhokla here sporty tall or warmth and
moisture like mosquitoes cotton Columba
bands protein llamo
miraculous birth leg but muscle bomber
flying on a jet supporti but my son Bawa
but we can say standard birth for for
people like us
Paducah Clarence Thunder Bajoran sport
Akita
it's called me okay nominee is a means
to be born in a womb of a woman yell
Cobra til I appear ahem Soren Juanita
and here's how it happens that Nene lots
are a tragedy now and you can find good
descriptions in the Vinaya scriptures
then a department mocha description baku
slalom kitab such even aya because they
are discussing when does the person
start come number a comma mask upon he'd
obsess R&D Malay and Buddhism says that
there is a living being at the moment of
conception then Buddhist Mohammed
ambassador the Marquis de Paris Artem
one
Pamela Palmer Palmer Cortana bomani of a
chip nobody apart tongue so it's kind of
a hallucination did it was much of a
leucine RC and the Pardo spirit being
that metal part oh no they enter the
womb become a master camera him and the
mother's blood menstrual blood and the
father's see minister then the remains
trustee put on our money so they have
this hallucination where they actually
they see their father and their mother
that man I come a minicar lucena see
support in Habana but normally had I had
a deep America and having sex but on sex
and they're like oh what's that it looks
very very fun Monica support the open
market so they come closer and closer
come on Monica and there's a tradition
here it says they're cha dong I
know this idiot can give me state this
they hurried to that place q RT America
boo boo boo kotappa tiptoe and then they
have different emotions alumina comma
Milliken was emotion the one I remember
my teacher describing that guru siamang
embark on yeah so it's called chart on
chart on means attracted and and
unattractive we post hoc tongue are piña
rhetoric contrapuntal
Jack means if the part of being for
example is going to be a male Chuck are
pina jicama clock Bardo Mesa like a
machete Soren lucky lucky then they see
sex going on and you know like all males
there what's that with this company have
sex tragedy then support the Maliki like
him like a belonging up I'd to up I -
then they see their father having the
sex and they feel competition or
something doesn't matter come here I am
brain company who began sixth America
brass are competitive but anyway they're
attracted by the sexual act that the
state think they see the Digimon upon
joke America tortora call it inductance
sexual America pickin broccoli huh
they may get start in the blood and the
singer America back to lambda rock and
iron money and they get frustrated
enough self that when I come my dearest
oscidyne kasam conquer a they dive
from their Bartle existence with a
feeling of kind of absurd and angry when
I come up get allocate open bar door
then I press on to dr. London morrow and
in Casey to need some
Jordan they make the crossing into the
new life come on yet stealing company
America mania Branca he decreed open
borrowed an actress on it to theta R key
la même dingdong Dane your natural turn
could you courage udom samba so what I
all of this section that I've described
to you so far and in this between some
more bucket and pull aside Alaskan
Kabaddi understand Joey need alum
rhetoric in E the
the contemplation on the source of the
truth of the source of suffering India
de l'opéra nuna and Ponca burner and a
resume burp underwritten we discussed
negative emotions in the last retreat
Yamaha spent on a mostly negative Garret
prep discuss the Karma those negative
emotions cause you to make emotional a
we've described how that karma forces
you into death into peridot and into a
new line then khatam Angeles cancer a
karma Maxo under menuju kamati and
cobalt Oh danke
go ahead open borrow this hope
presentation of how I get in trouble
with this noise it's a little person
taciturn charketa but con más allá de
the great panini
it's based on some famous learning books
be compatible Brahmaputra canal labrum
in general there are eight famous lemons
and an illuminated lapin bucola memory
monitor canal and actually this this
lemon which is in ninth one that's about
alum Remini rely on custom villain in
this one table okra pitcher in the 1920s
when he taught it he used all eight of
those can be subtly nearby Blanca
Rinpoche but I found some blah blahs dua
pulo on katika blue mana geranium and
good luck and some mualim Remini and at
this point in his lecture that but I
need a lamp enhancer Anya he says okay
this whole description that we've heard
in this retreat so far William a gothic
at Ballou description kita so the de but
Candela Brett rotz Giovanni that's based
on the middle length lamrim of Jessica
inhibitor a secondary lamrim Danone
panjang wananga alleged tsongkhapa
it's based on the path of bliss of the
first pension level but yes I can but
the path of bliss Jalan kabardian only
Panchen Lama pitamah and it's based on
the book called quick path which is by
His Holiness this second pension and his
thoughts are compatible and it's about
quick path talents but only he I'm only
up until now baka do
taani London Daniel K such a to me
searching but let's turn to a different
presentation which you don't really see
clearly in those elements to be
marketable alica presentation prepared
aya under the duckpin urban normally
Hutton Angeles talents a malam repeat oh
let's turn to the presentation of this
subject of how lousy is this liar as it
was presented in the great Mariquita
Balika present a seal subjected Amitabha
broke Rado panini supporting Lisa G
Candela Mumbai Messara only tsongkhapa
what outline just so copper use in his
very very famous the great book on the
steps of the path to describe how we get
into this trouble how we get into this
life a bugger is pasar el gouna can talk
about the Lambo could a great book on
the steps of her path bubu Sri Lanka
detail on a on top on Graham
Arkansas Akita Masuka darlin promise
Allah Nene Soraka Thomas column credo
panini and in so help us great book on
the steps of the tear Nabucco bizarre
Lankan the jalan on its own kappa he
uses the teaching of the twelve links of
dependent jaredstoughton cutter gun tuna
and we can kind of follow another book
called jump l Shalom which is called the
word of the gentle one the word of
manjushri
dan get up someone Google people cool
line but not my jump I'll sell you and
it's a boot
remediate aleihsalaam Ileana llama
kolima
subject some Shula oh sorry I'm just
gonna give you the outline and we're not
gonna go into much detail so I kinda got
massacred Italian alibied alum so we're
actually gonna move now to discussing
how the trouble starts but this term
we're gonna use the wheel of life
taquito my daughter can build us a
cotton cup about Sun bagaimana masala
Dumoulin that's let's go back to the
Turks death our country Kuwait Jordan
something stupid Chinna non Shepherd a
choke more look you can give this
explanation of how we get into sons are
based on that method we used up to know
mari kita come liquor tax Delia under be
some American Akita Masuka sansara
because our economy Torian get a good
knock on some basic Karen when cancer
nikishino jumbo source okey but I know
there's people in the audience today and
be the same with you these are power the
palmarosa Harini than somebody's an
under who are interested in the great
classics of Buddhism product event
classic pasar a Buddhist ma and that's
kind of the emphasis of our of our group
that need to Janice Punta Cana during
group Club Paquita we like to take the
time to go deeper and deeper keep dying
in my humble walk to the muscle to be
done I'm done mandala
and then we go into the classics and get
a Masuka get up get up cluster and here
/ bunker incisors DC NEPA Bukhari
pachamanca cotton if you're that kind of
person who were sick of cheap chicken
dadelus Oren summit a meeting in Moscow
clip eat alum car sake kept Akashi
deal like there for those kind of
special people it would be better to
give them the twelve links Ahmad so me -
Labib at no break America do a blast out
and then he jumps horses Danny coumadin
Leo Melamed topic and he starts to teach
the whole system of how we get into
trouble in this night that mullah
managers LaRue system banana rocket
Ahmedabad con más allá de la Vida bindi
based on this ancient teaching of The
Wheel of Life
but that's not a Canadian Coonoor Oh doc
I do pun so first he mentions a little
bit there about the history of The Wheel
of Life
did he pop a mobile home in your boot
cancer Dickinson jar Irondequoit open
when you kick Apple once upon a time
long ago the hulu kala the king of
central India rajadi
India Tonga and he doesn't say that
King's name but we know it was a kingdom
Arizona toppika toppika toes Raja
bimbisara he sent a gift to Takaaki
Calvo means to a king who was living in
the outlying person India North Central
in Nigeria Madea cursor on Raja young
tingly thereupon chill
Boogedy Tanaka India that King's name
was Diana sometimes they say with Triana
bimbisara this is special as I remember
is a special suit of armor seeing as I
ate two bacha bazi couscous and then let
me star accordant decide on something
more expensive to send back baby Sarah
Televisa minutos Costas Watanabe Mahalo
to de cream can come Bali
so I ended up he asked Lord Buddha Akira
Blio Britannia by the Buddha and Lord
Buddha directed the painting of the
Wheel of Life
da budem american-owned Tamil Lucas
Cranach a Dupin
and I've been studying that for many
years sorry nice llama but I think we
translate and we made a book about it
like 30 years aluminium - maken-ki toss
with a mother beat Canas and we
illustrated the work with
line drawings that we made not aluminum
back and Gomberg ambergris Ankita come
abroad kadala buckwheat Oh
you
based on the ancient stone carvings in
borobudur in Indonesia modest our canoe
Kiran bateau Qunari borobudur tea
Indonesia
you
and you can see here an image you seen
there's a elephant and on top of the
elephant there's a guy and the guy has a
box in his hands and Agatha's got a sort
of period and prior to my Maliki
quartered eating onion and he's
delivering this gift from the Messiah
King Ghidorah be Basara courage Audriana
and we translated that that story then
keep our country in the wheel of nine
petraju try another draught okay duper
Joe shake a teardrop means and there's a
recorded history
da-da-da-da-da-da pants ourselves how do
they honor when he saw the painting
earth of the twelve links top down
bottom animatronic atacama have no keys
on table fountain he got yo shake Yoshi
means this life is manda Petrenko Seabra
TR he to be anybody to buy the Pandora
pan so the bunker which is the Deepavali
Pachamama talkin let's follow those same
12 links and see if we can get the same
kind of feeling about man this life is
awesome
mary-kate I could T do a blast out on in
summer EE had a pock Akita be somewhere
about compressing salmon and Dan are
here to be neighbor know some and
return then we will want to get out Dan
communicating in black that's the goal
of this section it to lot to join the
rebellion in either a lump him
he also says gadget pachoo a $10 Lord
John searching till gonna get with Chum
ding Shih Tzu some bunkering betrayed in
his lecture arania also described how we
could develop these attitudes based on a
on a teaching by Gucci someone come back
and seek opinion but a circle a Jaron
geshe potowa
and
this - I lived a thousand years ago you
showed up three Bhutan in lalu and he
wrote a book about dependence began to
man and so we're gonna move on to this
teaching dependence and on a couple
Cantona Nene here you can see the whole
wheel of life painting listen I ended up
at Malia's Lulu Cassandra decreed upon
that was presented to King Day and asaji
can kabadi Raju Triana but I came in on
a hijabi Basara and I've studied there
are a few other suitors where Buddha
sends this painting to people sighs ah
da da da da da da ba ba ba sutrayana
muda me ammonium can Lucas anemic
epidural or sometimes he sends it to
people who would not be able to read a
suture intimacy some butter Sutra chica
blooming in America Sutra and those are
beautiful stories that you should study
solitary time dying and our supplies
recover there's a difference between the
Wheel of Life
and the twelve links Caracara billion
and our eradicate abandon do habla
Stoughton
the Wheel of Life includes the teaching
on the twelve links and here you see a
separation of the isolation of the 12
things the circle with the trauma so
ponto tombo blast out and undecided
Emily had permission to a blast out a
blinker and didn't do a blast out on so
technically the teaching on these twelve
links was presented separately from the
wheel also to disrupt Agnes and Jared
robust open-ended asaji kisara trapeze
under a raga Jukka we're gonna go back
to the text kita can come alley cat
Toxocara they're young Kia shoot chopper
sake cheer so to try to give us the same
feeling of being discouraged with this
line treatments about the mom breakin
get up residence on my it immediately
capital skater panini Journey we're
gonna we're gonna start with that as a
goal and we're gonna we're gonna go into
a new subject with that go get that
crowd more lighter than it was marketed
Matsoukas subject Peru do not you
Johnnie do we're gonna do you stand area
enlarge unity gonna we're gonna use the
twelve links Monica Robles fountain
conjunct are renaming some pate to do
our new contemplation about how terrible
this life is and how we got into this
trouble
blossom arute on the top American okay
to panini de mogi Monica taught early
but Allah promised alanya
now these twelve links were one of the
great sources for these twelve links
isn't teaching by lord buddha salah satu
somber booster on tourists out on e near
the larger and some buddha in tibetan is
called salud young widow which you see
here the lamas up tibetan it is about
salud junk Pedroia and earlier this
evening
though and in sanskrit alabaster shall
istanbul sutra it'll actually stop a
sutra which means as the sutra about a
sprout of rice the artists who taught
and talk to us for us and he says that's
really where this idea of this waffling
started out you should return it to
brother
acai did or lost out on the moonlight on
and about Sonia then he quotes that
suture briefly Naruto hey Andy a bit
dejan DK DK WA
okay very famous Anika Panama Canal in
in that sutras develops to try to Lord
Buddha starts the discussion would you
like this could see by saying if if this
is here then this is gonna be here in
Sydney mokkania country jetty mechana
can you see me and if this thing starts
then this thing's gonna start a holiday
Dumoulin maka holiday Academy and the
hope trouble starts with
misunderstanding the world that's a
little masala d Mulligan and Casa la
palma dunya
then we start to make camera don't get
mm about Karma
etc etc that's through service and he he
doesn't say more from this term a lot
economy by dr. Seuss
I really like that so castle tried to
sell I'm gonna inject a little bit of
the city in today's session that is our
menu Dickens Attica DC suit reduce se
hurry me it's gonna make the session a
little longer
what's a city city cat Lobby la mine I
don't care do listen
just be patient Chucky but Sabella and
this is fun done any minion on come and
we're gonna go deeper muscle could be
that's the way we're doing the steps in
the pen okay Tom lakukan Lanka long
Khadija lon so here's I like the first
paragraph or two of that so I sue
Collini Mir Appa Appa do I dare is to
try to and I've included it in the
reading for you that's I'm when you're
Dalembert ananda gandha dealer
chum then the Chiquita poor Tom Jake
campaign now because the Buddha knows
everything there is in the whole
universe
Buddha toggle Anya photo in this little
alum samastah he said to this monks who
came to the teaching lab ricotta kepada
para pyramid and got on larger calendar
hey you must hike a lien para be Robin
see attention Jared to authority to Tomo
anyone who sees that things happen in
dependence on each other
yeah Papa normally hahaha lantern-jawed
Etrigan do not to some align the person
who understands dependence understands
my diamond or on yamaneika Prague and
Amani Toomer Mohammed our Messiah and
anyone who understands sorry let's put
it this way disease that things work in
dependence on each other so tempura
Amalia bhavasagara Albuquerque
don't even start to summer liner that
person sees the wielder Oh Ronnie -
Melea dar - Lee and if a person sees
that will turn the jika so Sora normally
heard our message out to eat too deep
elders kept a gun to them then they saw
my camera calmly had sung Buddha case so
who said shopping Upper Canada sang
Buddha okay if you see how things depend
on each other
chicken double hetero Cigala halter gun
- so - so Molina then you saw my
children mark and Amelia Thomas and
Josiah if you see my children and you
can mm Thomas and Josiah then you
actually have fire
consciousness so everyone of course the
month I said oh what's this dependency
we want to see there is more wrong para
BR one but captain got enemy coming in
Mali happy occasion what is dependent
copy up I took a Top Gun - knocking
shopping beats our attention there are
Jewish attorney you want to know what
dependencies
I think it did that a well here's how it
is beginni
do you pay did you if this happens this
happens you can literally in your
country jadi djp tici tici and if this
starts then that's gonna spread you
kinda more like a token Malaya okay and
then they they're like well what do you
mean that America's party if you don't
understand the world in our Chicana to
the monarchy dunya
if you misunderstand we can develop
Ramadan dunya then you're gonna make
mccracken about karma if you make her
cheek and about karma you make awareness
and a vodka so darin if you make
awareness you can dama but Cassandra you
make body and mind under mama to Buddha
be Kira if you make party in mind you
can't about to but a big unit you make
the six stores of sense I'm damned
important up in to Indra if you have the
6th army leaked in a bid to Indra you
may contact what contact in the dunya
world
if you make contact with yourself you
can do but contact in the dunya you are
in you're gonna feel feelings not
conduct remember a second person if you
feel feelings you can do more a
superfund desires gonna start mock
opinion academic desire studies are
going in and malai if desired growth
yoga hospitable
you will people anaconda here
if you are born then G gondola here you
must get old and you must die and the
Harris method it 200 Hertz party and you
appear you suffer dr. Morita you will
cry out and I mean I can meniscus are
Keaton more and more pale in you know
some Arkansas sake Dunham Peter Panda
and more and more sadness in your heart
dance uh di dalam happy under and then
truly chaos then comedian burner burner
cut song this whole like so little
heater PD is a mountain of pain Idol
Ossabaw good opener eaten then I think
everybody danced a because Arisaka not
appear piranha
I think automatically everyone in the
room or everyone in the field cursor
automatism oral deal wrong and a touch
more until Apollo are to put is like
Mayo entity belong Tita masala Merrick
but gob adj card if you stop
misunderstanding your world you won't
make this back condom on Veronica's
Alabama at random duniya that did a
comma but karma anymore you don't have
this negative awareness you can tell
about karma lucky and at the demo Maliki
cuz under a negative and kita Maliki
if you don't have that kind of awareness
you're not gonna pick up a painful body
and mind inside chicken adobo Milliken
father and supper Tito under dr. manga
bill to Buddha and Akira no saki de la
me Blanca
you stop that mortal body and mind
inside your mom you're not gonna have
this since the condiment icon to Buddha
became and fauna
dalam to Evo under under tada karma
Maliki Indra as painful sin indra and
ryan when your kid canítö if you can
stop there you can get up and eat
painful contact with the world
makanda Tita mom what contact my kids
can read on dunya if you stop painful
contact with the world dick and among
hunty can contact when your kid can't
even dunya then you stop painful
feelings no condom on and decompress on
circuit if you stop those feelings you
can decompress ani - you'll start an
antique inherit our if you stop the
beginning of desire you will stop the
more deep kinds of desert chicken divan
antique inherit our wall maka under
Deaconess Hospital appeasement not that
it says desired then you won't trigger
the Karma at death which you can double
her thicken up so some mandala be to
makanda to Dhaka mamizou karma but come
at it a bit Soraka by the way I think I
forgot to mention it saya because a blue
bomb in a bootcut pants alumna cited
among the but--can and sati to topic arm
under the Pichu
if you stop how the chemistry Uganda
manhunt Dickens are Carmen tibideaux
then you can stop having these deadly
rivers knock on door antimatter but can
to book on her on a moment economy if he
stopped this deadly you can damaja
deacon coherent companion mama t economy
no more aging and death in the old way
Makati da de la keepin wondered come
attendants are a llama
no more certain aesthetic ideological so
deal Morris trying out in pain did up a
delegate on its on qussuk eaten no more
physical thing to the catalog year or so
circuit physic no more mental pain to
the catalog use equipment down and no
more of the chaos of this life that did
I
logic Arkansas and LMU to be me that's
how you stop this big mountainous that
begitu lotta romantic and Ginobili
panini and this concludes the statement
the first big stable my lord
Nalini Akira Parata and Boozer pertama
only Son Buddha the reader a blast out
there last thing before he stops caring
ultracal so don't get a brandy couple
things I'd like to share with you an
apology himself some bacon Kappa Rhonda
so you know we have
group of translators they are
translating ancient books and the target
address clump up under my yarmulke buku
buku Kuna and we chose 18 of the most
important great ancient classics from
each of the great schools coming Amelia
clapping Blas beaucoup classes but Sir
Kuno Pauline panting very massive
massive school of the Sarah and one of
the books we are translating committed
to mark on the translator is su Gong XI
who is also from the last to cancion de
cabra thundery Indonesia that Singapore
he's translating a very deep very
detailed very long book about these
traveling's the eminent Jamaican dinner
son of mandalam sana P&G bukit panjang
blah blah Stoughton it was written I
checked
1550 so the big Saudi to least get our
town
sbrick sobbing tragedy didn't occur
Agora bar a parasite in do they estimate
this was a year that Shakespeare is
break America Kira Connie to town
Shakespeare la hero and and this is the
year that Michael and Michael Angelo did
some famous when he taught a lot on
Michael I'm the la coubre palookas on
token of the Italian so we're about to
go into the twelve links from The Wheel
of Life
did he get a cat Massacre could do a
blast out under your Annika he do pun
but if you're a very ambitious student
who has to go deep deep deep competing
under sort on plunger and something I'm
used to standing in muscle Jojo Mandela
and I strongly suggest you go read the
translation that Sugeng has finished so
far he's not finished with the whole
book but he's almost finished
makasar Saran can under my budget
Rajamani ensue Gonzalez honest I can say
Johnny Diablo milliseconds little bukata
Padilla habilis fire yeah we're gonna
up here for you the link to the to the
website attack on memory condition it
out on casitas website now all those 18
translations that we are working on
somewhat lappam blasts are German and
Kimiko jackin the greatest books of the
greatest ghosts of the last two
attributes are dari scholars contrabass
are the adorable Amara to stuff on track
here you can go read them for free undo
it and they'd be somewhat Sonia sorry
gratis DC to online we call our little
group the unofficial official name is
mixed nuts come in when you boot club
pocket El Camino Morrow's make it across
miss about cutting some poor on mixed
nuts
yes we're all a little bit crazy can I
get us some most wicked Gila and we come
from a whole mixture different cultures
in the world and I got me to cut a
tongue that is little sample and good I
embed a di dunia so you know if you
really want to go deeper into this
subject the did Uganda but they're
burning it must be delicate subject I
strongly suggest you go read sooo gangs
translation which is available for free
on the website so it's a company run
commander Mumbai chatter - man soo Kyung
and Prasad yet even grab this PC to swim
now if you get excited about that scar
on G Gundam and JD but some Agathon
Tonya and someday you want to learn
translation yes sir so - Hari I'm dying
and blood job touch upon some Deary
you have 300,000 bucks not 18 we need
help
Tigger a to three boo boo boo consume at
la pomme blasphemy boo to bunt one then
you should start listening to those
translation classes now Kandahar small m
and n are gonna class cluster Germany -
are they difficult yes they are
difficult
apakah solid yeah solid will you get
confused at the beginning yes you will
get confused I can't be going to owl de
yeah now I can being on the wall now
will you be like master shrine song back
in the Tang Dynasty who's started a
whole tradition for a billion people
abakada a cancer party master Chang
Chang Balika dynasty tongue
you mobilize little tradition to
familiar or run you know you can help
yeah and that be some abun - so there
are 600 free translation classes online
ad and emeritus class for German gratis
online go to youtube look at YouTube
it's called Tibetan language channel
sorry - baton language channel solder on
bass atiba maybe if you're very
interested in the twelve links you can
design a preparing didn't do a blast out
on you can follow the classes together
and there be somebody could be class
young sugan it could be which is almost
a hundred class now hum Paris reduce
costs okay now it's Karan if you're very
ambitious you can just suck an ambitious
like you really wanna go deep deep DVD
chika undying in by the Dharma so I
think those classes sigh bigger class
class it to which are being held in this
building in the Sedona College of
International Management Institute on
Arizona USA like an Academy need deeper
grunting is under the management
international this Adana Arizona
Americas Rica we are covering every
major school of twenty five centuries of
Buddhism Camila put this except sakala
odometer in to apply Lima abut Buddhist
man
and I'm putting up here an email address
than some American DC nyalam an email of
nicosia Nicholas Shaw who's the director
of the program director program Indy
those programs are held three times a
year for two weeks program program for
somebody idea cantika college towns
LeMond Domingo
I think I think truly it's one of the
big moment in history so epic and even
urban da da de la Salle's a to moment
bizarre the lobster Chara and to me we
would love to have you come
Maggie saya Commission on you can that
happen you started as an observer in
under mullah Mohammed Nicholas and then
slowly you become matured bran lon under
budget depend on Chama and here's a
picture of one of the class but he's got
a delegate battery salah satu Colossus
and i would love to see than science
anomaly up under the sauna
very very welcome to come under some hot
summer this summer to look up and I
believe it's one of the most important
things in this world
concerts are near the Las Olas Italian
public but indeed Unni a me so that
session tell the Dean is a seekers Pulu
thanks to Stanley terima kasih Stacy
team for getting it all organized rima
così team so the monitor samanya and
we're about to step into the wheel of
life but kita akan milanka could
elaborate and see one keep some company
sir see the surplus